[

_Connectify Hotspot_Virtual Router & Wi-Fi Repeater](#)[

_Speedify_Channel Bonding VPN for Speed, Security & Stability](https://speedify.com/)[

_Pingify_Network Diagnostics Made Easy](https://pingify.me/)[

_EdgeWise_Increased Reliability at the Edge of Wi-Fi](https://edgewise.app/)

Privacy Policy
==============

**EFFECTIVE DATE 10/18/2009; UPDATED 5/31/2018**

Connectify, Inc. (“Connectify,” “we,” “us”) respects your privacy and as such we strive to collect the minimal amount of information necessary to operate our service. This Privacy Policy explains the type of information we collect through our website at connectify.me (the “Site”) and the Connectify Hotspot application, and how we use this information to provide outstanding value to you.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, you should contact us at [privacy@connectify.me](mailto:privacy@connectify.me).

#### How do you Protect the Privacy of my Connectify Sessions?

We do not log IP addresses, sites, or data that you send or receive through the Connectify Hotspot application.

Communication to our backend servers and databases are encrypted with SSL and firewalled to restrict access to only authorized servers. Furthermore, access to customer data is limited only to employees who require access in the delivery of the service.

#### What Personal Information We Collect

**Contact information:** We receive contact information from customers who buy our products through the Fastspring store. This includes name, phone number, email address, personal address, and company name. Customers who create an account for the Connectify Hotspot application may provide an email address.

**Homepage Access Logs:** Our servers log access to our homepage, including IP address, page accessed, browser type and operating system.

**Device Information:** In order to prevent piracy, Connectify Hotspot may access and report unique device identifiers such as Hostname, MAC or UUID.

**Location Information:** Connectify Hotspot collects what country you appear to be in using an IP-based approximation, in order to tailor special offers.

**Cookies:** Our websites store cookies and similar technology, like single-pixel gifs, that help us optimize our website design. Cookies are text files containing small amounts of information downloaded to your device when you visit a website. The entity that placed the cookie on your browser can then read the unique information on that cookie. The Connectify Hotspot application does not require any registration to use the service. To read more about our cookie policy, click [here.](https://www.connectify.me/cookie-policy)

**Support Requests:** We may request more information when you contact our support. As appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name and email address.

#### How Does Connectify Use This Information?

**To provide services:**

* For the authentication of users and devices
* Communication about your account, subscription status, or license

**To send emails and other communications:**

* Including advertising new features, software updates, or new products
* Marketing messages, such as new promotions or company stories
* We provide an opt-out for communications unnecessary for the delivery of our services.

**To respond to support requests:**

* Support staff may request identifying information to verify your account status.

#### Does Connectify Disclose Information to Outside Parties?

We will not sell or rent your personal information to other companies. Additionally, we cannot disclose information about the services, websites, or applications you utilize while connected to our Services as we do not store this information.

Except as described below, we will not disclose your personal information to outside parties.

* Third Party Service Providers – See list of trusted third parties below for more detail.
* Legal Compliance – We do not log what you do through our servers, so we do not have any such information to provide to law enforcement or anyone else. Outside of this, we, like all companies, need to comply with the legal process including court orders and other requests from law enforcement and regulatory authorities.
* Assignment – We reserve the right to transfer personal information to a new entity or third party as part of a merger, acquisition, reorganization, sale of some or all of our assets, joint venture, assignment, transfer, or other disposition of all or any portion of our business, assets, or stock (including, without limitation, in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings). We will notify you via email or prominent notice on our web site if the third party’s or new entity’s treatment of personal information will materially differ from the treatment described in this Privacy Policy.

#### Third Party Service Providers

**Google Analytics**

Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google. Google utilizes the data collected to track and examine the use of the Service to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services. Google may use the data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. Personal data collected: Cookie and Usage Data. Place of processing: USA. Find Google’s privacy policy [here](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en).

#### Additional Rights

Individuals located in certain countries, including the European Economic Area, have certain statutory rights in relation to their personal data. Subject to any exemptions provided by law, you may have the right to request access to Information, as well as to seek to update, delete or correct this Information.

To request access, deletion or correction of your personal information, email us at [privacy@connectify.me](mailto:privacy@connectify.me).

#### Protecting the Privacy of Children

Our Services are not intended for use by children under the age of eighteen (18) and are not directed at such children. Please do not register at Connectify if you are under the age of eighteen (18). We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of thirteen (13). If you have information about a child using our service, please contact [privacy@connectify.me](mailto:privacy@connectifv.me).

#### Transferring Personal Data from the EU to the US

Connectify has its headquarters in the United States. Information we collect from you will be processed in the United States. The United States has not sought nor received a finding of “adequacy” from the European Union under Article 45 of the GDPR. Connectify relies on derogations for specific situations as set forth in Article 49 of the GDPR. In particular, Connectify collects and transfers to the U.S. personal data only: with your consent; to perform a contract with you; or to fulfill a compelling legitimate interest of Connectify in a manner that does not outweigh your rights and freedoms. Connectify endeavors to apply suitable safeguards to protect the privacy and security of your personal data and to use it only consistent with your relationship with Connectify and the practices described in this Privacy Policy. Connectify also minimizes the risk to your rights and freedoms by not collecting or storing sensitive information about you.

#### Data Storage and Retention

Your personal data is stored by Connectify on its servers, and on the servers of the cloud-based database management services Connectify engages, which may be located in the United States. Connectify retains data for the duration of the customer’s or member’s business relationship with Connectify. For more information on where and how long your personal data is stored, and for more information on your rights of erasure and portability, please contact the Connectify’s data protection officer at [privacy@connectify.me](mailto:privacy@connectify.me).

#### Data Protection Authority

Subject to applicable law, you also have the right to (i) restrict Connectify's use of your personal data and (ii) lodge a complaint with your local data protection authority or the Irish Data Protection Commissioner, which Connectify has designated as its lead supervisory authority in the European Union. If you are a resident of the European Economic Area and believe we maintain your Personal Data within the scope of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), you may direct questions or complaints to our lead supervisory authority:

Irish Data Protection Commissioner Office of the Data Protection Commissioner Canal House, Station Road, Portarlington, Co. Laois, R32 AP23, Ireland Phone +353 57 868 4757 Fax: +353 57 868 4757 Email: [info@dataprotection.ie](https://www.connectify.me/privacy-policy/info@dataprotection.ie)

#### Changes to Our Privacy Policy

If this policy is updated, we will post changes on this page and update the Privacy Policy modification date. If we make any changes to this Privacy Policy that materially affect our practices with regard to the personal information we have previously collected from you, we will endeavor to provide you with notice in advance of such change by highlighting the change on the Site.

#### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact Connectify: For Privacy Questions: [privacy@connectify.me](https://www.connectify.me/privacy-policy/privacy@connectify.me) For Other Questions: support@connectify.me By Mail: 601 Spring Garden, 3rd floor, Philadelphia, PA 19123 USA

###### Solutions

* [Best WiFi Range Extender: Use Your Own Laptop with Connectify Hotspot](https://connectify.me/best-wifi-range-extender/)
* [Wireless Repeater Right on Your Windows PC with Connectify Hotspot](https://connectify.me/wifi-wireless-repeater/)

* [How to Set Up a WiFi Mobile Hotspot with Windows 10 and Your Laptop](https://connectify.me/blog/how-to/create-laptop-hotspot-windows-10/)

###### Company

###### Follow Us
